(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
#hololivefes EXPO25_DAY1
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a while until the performance starts.
Attention
ご来場のお客様へ
For Visitors
演出の都合上照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK.
PENLIGHT COLORS
バンダイ・BANDAI SPIRITSより、
From Bandai and BANDAI SPIRITS,
ホロライブデフォルメコレクション Vol.2
2025年8月発売予定
hololive Deformed Collection Vol.2
Coming August 2025
hololive EXPO 2025の会場内にある特設ブースで
at the special booth within the hololive EXPO 2025 venue,
ホロライブ カプセルラバーマスコット Bright Parade 4
2025年3月発売予定
hololive Capsule Rubber Mascot Bright Parade 4
Coming March 2025
展示中の商品をご紹介！
introducing products currently on display!
hololive CITY '24 ダイカットステッカーセット
好評発売中
hololive CITY '24 Die-cut Sticker Set
On Sale Now
一番くじ ホロライブ ~Cyberpunk Style~
2025年3月21日(金)より順次発売予定
Ichiban Kuji hololive ~Cyberpunk Style~
Sequential release starting March 21, 2025
ホロライブ IF -Relax time- / ホロライブ IF petit
hololive IF -Relax time- / hololive IF petit
hololive EXPO 2025限定の、
Exclusive to hololive EXPO 2025,
一番くじ特設フォトブースも展開中。
the Ichiban Kuji special photo booth is also open.
モニターをタッチしてくじ券をめくり、
Touch the monitor to flip the lottery ticket,
出てきたデザインと一緒に撮影できます。
and you can take a photo with the design that appears.
グッスマ
GoodSma
hololive 5th fes. で歌われた名曲
The masterpiece sung at hololive 5th fes.
The Last Frontier からなんと！
From 'The Last Frontier' comes...!
フィギュア化決定！
Figure production confirmed!
あの感動をもう一度...
Experience that emotion once again...
1/7スケールフィギュア化決定
星街すいせい　AZKi
1/7 scale figure production confirmed
Hoshimachi Suisei, AZKi
フリューから『ホロライブ』プライズが全国アミューズメント施設に続々展開中！
FuRyu 'hololive' prizes are now appearing in amusement centers nationwide!
4月からは新たにひっかけフィギュアも登場！
New 'Hikkake' figures will also be available starting in April!
フリュー
FuRyu
台湾旅行中、最も便利な決済サービスを提供します。
We provide the most convenient payment service for your travels in Taiwan.
新商品まもなく登場！
New products coming soon!
Color Rise Harmony 一卡通限定盲包
Color Rise Harmony iPASS Limited Blind Bags
歌いたい曲が入っていなかった…
The song I wanted to sing wasn't there...
だったら JOYSOUND X1 で歌おうぜ！
In that case, let's sing with JOYSOUND X1!
JOYSOUND X1! ONLY NUMBER ONE!
JOYSOUND X1! 曲数 NUMBER ONE!
JOYSOUND X1! Number one in song count!
AIが採点 絶賛 カラオケ最高最高！
AI scoring, highly acclaimed, karaoke is the best, the best!
曲数No.1 歌いたい曲があるって最高
Number 1 in song count! It's the best to have the songs you want to sing
JOYSOUND X1
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention: For Visitors
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance
声出し応援 OK です
Cheering loudly is OK
hololive 6th fes. Color Rise Harmony
hololive STAGE2
バンダイ・バンダイスピリッツより、
From Bandai and Bandai Spirits,
ホロライブEXPO 2025の会場にある特設ブースで、
at the special booth in the hololive EXPO 2025 venue,
展示中の商品をご紹介！
we're introducing the products on display!
ホロライブEXPO 2025限定の、
Exclusive to hololive EXPO 2025,
一番くじ特設フォトブースも展開中。
the Ichiban Kuji special photo booth is also open.
モニターをタッチしてくじ券をめくり、
Touch the monitor to flip the lottery ticket,
出てきたデザインと一緒に撮影できます。
and you can take a photo with the design that appears.
GOOD SMILE COMPANY!
The Last Frontier
刻みつけ
Engraving it...
捧げる歌を
A song to offer...
追い求め
Seeking it...
旅立つ歌を
A song for the journey...
フリューから『ホロライブ』プライズが
全国アミューズメント施設にて続々展開中！
Hololive prizes from FuRyu are appearing
in amusement facilities nationwide!
フリュー
FuRyu
90人のhololiveとHOLOSTARSタレントから
好きな1人を選ぼう！
Choose your favorite from 90
hololive and HOLOSTARS talents!
3月8日より先行予約開始
Pre-orders start March 8
台湾旅行中、最も便利な決済サービスを提供します。
Providing the most convenient payment service
while traveling in Taiwan.
新商品まもなく登場！
New products coming soon!
hololive 6th fes. 一カード通限定盲包
hololive 6th fes. iPASS Limited Blind Pack
だったらJOYSOUND X1で歌おうぜ！
Then let's sing with JOYSOUND X1!
JOYSOUND X1 on the way!
JOYSOUND X1 曲数 No.1!
JOYSOUND X1, number one in song count!
AIが採点絶賛 カラオケ最高！
AI scoring is great, karaoke is the best!
JOY EVOLUTION!
歌いたい曲があるって最高！
It's great to have the songs you want to sing!
JOYSOUND X1
タイトー
Taito
超特大ぬいぐるみブランド『どきゅーと』から
商品化決定！
Product release decided from the
super-oversized plushie brand 'Doqute'!
約100cmサイズ ぬいぐるみに！
Becoming roughly 100cm size plushies!
グルーヴコースター最新作に、白上フブキと...
In the latest Groove Coaster game, Shirakami Fubuki and...
...さくらみこがキャラクターボイスで参戦！
...Sakura Miko join with character voices!
人気曲や、私たちが歌う曲も楽しめる！
You can enjoy popular songs and songs we sing!
私たちがグルーヴワールドをナビゲートするよ！
We'll navigate the Groove World!
コラボイベント実施中！
Collaboration event in progress!
コナミ
Konami
ゲームのオアシスに飛び込め！
Dive into the gaming oasis!
GiGO
PalVerse フィギュア化決定！
PalVerse figure production decided!
PalVerse Pale. フィギュア化決定！
PalVerse Pale. figure production decided!
白上フブキ・大神ミオ フィギュア化決定
Shirakami Fubuki and Ookami Mio figure production decided
宝鐘マリン 1/7スケールフィギュア 締切間近
Houshou Marine 1/7 scale figure deadline approaching
SHIBUYA TSUTAYA IP書店 × Design COCO
新ブランド始動 AXGRIT
SHIBUYA TSUTAYA IP Bookstore x Design COCO
new brand launch: AXGRIT
推しの夢叶えます。 明利酒類
Making your oshi's dream come true. Meiri Shurui
特報
Special News
2025年夏 コラボカフェ・プライズ 開催決定
Collaboration Cafe & Prizes decided for Summer 2025!
hololive 6th fes. Color Rise Harmony
#hololivefesEXPO25_DAY1
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援 OK です
Attention: To all visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK
hololive 6th fes. Color Rise Harmony
PENLIGHT COLORS
Color Rise Harmony
応援メッセージ
Support Messages
Color Rise Harmony
hololive 6th fes.
AZKi
紫咲シオン
Murasaki Shion
兎田ぺこら
Usada Pekora
宝鐘マリン
Houshou Marine
天音かなた
Amane Kanata
尾丸ポルカ
Omaru Polka
鷹嶺ルイ
Takane Lui
風真いろは
Kazama Iroha
アユンダ・リス
Ayunda Risu
パヴォリア・レイネ
Pavolia Reine
こぼ・かなえる
Kobo Kanaeru
森カリオペ
Mori Calliope
小鳥遊キアラ
Takanashi Kiara
ハコス・ベールズ
Hakos Baelz
火威青
Hiodoshi Ao
音乃瀬奏
Otonose Kanade
一条莉々華
Ichijou Ririka
儒烏風亭らでん
Juufuutei Raden
轟はじめ
Todoroki Hajime
hololive 6th fes.
Color Rise Harmony
あの涙が 今の僕らを繋げて
Those tears connect us now
この空に 君の欠片がいるから
Because your fragments are in this sky
一人じゃないから
Because you are not alone
空描いた文字の中
Inside the letters drawn in the sky
目を閉じた先に 色づく景色が揺れた
Beyond my closed eyes, the colorful scenery swayed
少し戸惑う 風の中
In the slightly confusing wind
重なる花びら 私たちの声
Overlapping petals, our voices
一瞬 一瞬
Instant by instant
捕まえるみたいに
As if to capture it
もっと もっと
More and more
踏み出せたらいいな
I wish I could step forward
あの涙が 今の僕らを繋げて
Those tears connect us now
この空に 君の欠片がいるから
Because your fragments are in this sky
強くなってもいい 今の光を
It's okay to become strong, take this light
僕ら 集め空に放つ
We gather and release it into the sky
この奇跡を 僕らでそっと輝かせるから
We will gently make this miracle shine
Color Rise Harmony
どんな種も 握りしめ
Holding any seed tightly
遠い未来へと 強く願い込め
With a strong wish for the distant future
今日も明日も 風に吹かれては
Today and tomorrow, being blown by the wind
理想の花びら 彩る明日の空
Ideal petals, coloring tomorrow's sky
何百億も
Tens of billions
光る星みたいに
Like shining stars
ずっと ずっと
Always, always
終わらないから
Because it will never end
この笑顔が 過去強く抱きしめて
May this smile embrace the past tightly
今未来に この手伸ばしてゆくから
Now, I'm reaching out my hand to the future
時に転んでも 空を見上げよう
Even if we stumble sometimes, let's look up at the sky
笑い 日々を刻んでゆく
Laughing, we carve out our days
次の夢を 掴み取るって約束するから
I promise to seize the next dream
踏み出そう ここから
Let's step forward from here
We are with you
はじまり 未来色を見ていたい
I want to see the colors of the beginning and the future
あの夢手にしたい
I want to grasp that dream
We are with you, capture the moment
その先まで 続く空に紛れたら
If I blend into the sky that stretches beyond...
君の場所と 今を繋ぎたくて
I want to connect where you are with the now
あの涙が 今の僕らを繋げて
Those tears connect us now
この心に 君の欠片がいるから
Because fragments of you are in this heart
強くなってもいい 今の光を
It's okay to become stronger, the light of now
僕ら集め 空に放つ
We gather it and release it to the sky
この軌跡を 僕らずっと輝かせるから
Because we'll make this miracle shine forever
咲かせよう ここから
Let it bloom from here
一人じゃないから
Because you're not alone
We are with you!
POW POW POW POW POW POW POW POW POW POW
やっほー！ポルカだよ～
Yahoo! It's Polka!
ってあれ、出オチじゃねーかって？
Wait, you're saying that's a predictable opening?
とりあえず声出して、いくぞ～～～！
First of all, make some noise! Here we go!
お～ありがとなお調子！
Oh, thanks for the energy!
センキュー幕張！
Thank you, Makuhari!
Na na na na... Ready for the show?
Okay, 激動独壇場
Okay, the Gekidou monopoly stage
Let's go, let's go!
Na na na na... Ready for the show?
カバケ！
Go wild!
Ya ya ya ya SHOW TIME!
底辺のなりおりゃおいえ
Lowering myself down, here we go
良い子コンピどうりゃ oh hell yeah
Good child competition, oh hell yeah
段々ノリノリで上等 bam bam bam bam!
Getting more and more excited, bam bam bam bam!
エモい笑えない 宴の Party Stop
Emotional and speechless, the party stops here
Are you guys ready?
Ready, set, go!
愛称 地にも畜生 悲劇の声だから 堂々と Bang
Nickname, even on earth, damn it! It's the voice of tragedy, so proudly Bang
もうガランどう 疾うの疾う あちらを向こう かわるがわるに Ah
Already empty, long ago, let's head over there, one after another, Ah
格好つけたつもりは オーマチックにあふれちゃう
Didn't mean to look cool, it just overflows automatically
宴の様 壇上の上で はしゃげ 奏で
Like a banquet, on the stage, frolic and play
らったたた おいで
Ra-ta-ta-ta, come here
Nah nah nah nah I'm ready for the show
万歳 遊ぶ気に寿 Shout it out, shout it out
Banzai! Celebration in the mood to play, Shout it out, shout it out
Nah nah nah nah I'm ready for the show
あまり 感動に八十跳び Shout it out, shout it out
So moved, leaping eighty times, Shout it out, shout it out
Hey!
Come on everyone!
くらっちゃいな
Take this!
らったたたた
Ra-ta-ta-ta-ta
Hey!
満開 損益に飛び切り Jump around
Full bloom, leap beyond profit and loss, Jump around
Look at me now 日々を揺るがす音 跳ねる心臓
Look at me now, the sound that shakes the days, a leaping heart
Cry 激情 敵陣上 Ready...
Cry, passion, above the enemy line, Ready...
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe 最大級の業 業 業 隠れん坊
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe, the greatest karma, karma, karma, hide and seek
一足お先に持ち帰り 放て 蛇崩 意気地も
Going home a step ahead, release it, Jabakure, and your courage too
ジャバラダダビ 飾らぬ舞い舞い 延伸した末のイノセンス
Jabara-da-da-bi, an unadorned dance, innocence at the end of extension
たってかってなっちゃいや カルマに誰もが謳えば
Don't want it to be selfish, if everyone sings to karma
ジャバラダダビ 飾らぬ舞い舞い 延伸した末のイノセンス
Jabara-da-da-bi, an unadorned dance, innocence at the end of extension
声も躍るさあ
The voice also dances, come on
お好きに
As you like
乱心 正気に あれ 相乗 悉くに
Madness, back to sanity, that synergy, entirely
ほだされても 止まらない Yeah
Even if I'm bound, I won't stop, Yeah
衝動に塗装し 描いた Daybreak How goes it down now
Painted over the impulse, the Daybreak I drew, How goes it down now
Nah nah nah nah I'm ready for the show
異例の 危険な 非のない 比較 充満
Extraordinary, dangerous, faultless, comparison, full
Nah nah nah nah I'm ready for the show
12 12 爆破だ
1 2 1 2, it's a blast
Nah nah nah nah I'm ready for the show
万歳 遊ぶ気に寿 Shout it out, shout it out
Banzai! Celebration in the mood to play, Shout it out, shout it out
Nah nah nah nah I'm ready for the show
喝采 巻き起こすために Stay 逆境 忘れて Shout it out
To stir up applause, Stay, forget the adversity, Shout it out
右に左まとめて らったったった Pull up
Left and right all together, ra-ta-ta-ta, Pull up
思い切りに
With all my might
くらっちゃいな 何はともあれ ご賞味 Shout it out, shout it out
Take this! Anyway, enjoy, Shout it out, shout it out
Thank you!
苦い恋の果て 残された泥沼
At the end of a bitter love, the left-over quagmire
不明の鐘の山
A mountain of unidentified bells
あいつの気配がするものは 未練ばかりで気色悪いな
Things that feel like them are just lingering attachments and gross
あたし生きながら化けて出る
I'll come back as a ghost while still alive
鏡の前で早変わり
A quick change in front of the mirror
バイバイ 仮面で通しましょう
Bye-bye, let's keep the mask on
今宵もひと暴れ
Another rampage tonight
踊れ 踊り 踊れ
Dance, dancing, dance
乱れ髪 弾む胸
Disheveled hair, a bouncing chest
桃源郷の罠に酔いしれて
Intoxicated by the traps of Shangri-La
Shine a spot!
ライト見な
Look at the lights
バイバイ バイバイバイバイやったー
Bye-bye, bye-bye-bye-bye, yay!
バイバイ 仮面は台無しぞ
Bye-bye, the mask is ruined
バイバイ バイバイバイバイやったー
Bye-bye, bye-bye-bye-bye, yay!
黄金の蝶 舞い上がれ
Golden butterfly, soar high
ほらほら踊れや 三々五々 感謝祭
Hey hey, dance away, in small groups, Thanksgiving
切な 追い越せよ
Overtake the sadness
瞬間 喰らい尽くす
Devour the moment
浮世よ 忘れて更ける 壇上ハイ ぱいやぱいや
Floating world, forget it and grow late; Stage High, paiya paiya
ミスティック・クイ バイバイ仮面
Mystic Queen, Bye Bye Mask
悪い奴だと知りつつも 恋は盲目 止めどなく
Knowing you're a bad guy, love is blind and relentless
愛のために血も青くした 私は戸惑いを消し去る
I even made my blood blue for love, I'll wipe away the confusion
虫かごの鳥 飛ばなきゃ 虫けらのままで終わっちまう
If the bird in the cage doesn't fly, it'll end up just a bug
バイバイ 仮面を解き放つ 今宵も羽ばたけよ
Bye bye, release the mask; flap your wings tonight as well
喰らえ 喰らえ 喰らえ 獣よ 偽物よ
Eat it, eat it, eat it, oh beast, oh fake
門出よ さらば 与えられぬ
A departure, farewell, I cannot be given
シャイなスポート シャイなスポート シャイなスポート ライト浴びな
Shy sport, Shy sport, Shy sport, bathe in the light
バ バ バ ババ ぱいやぱいや バイバイ 仮面は毒っぽ
Ba ba ba baba paiya paiya, Bye bye mask is poisonous
バ バ バ ババ ぱいやぱいや 視線の先 スキャンダル
Ba ba ba baba paiya paiya, an upcoming scandal at the end of my gaze
ト ト ドン 揺らせよ ラッシュアワーにバイブレーション
To to don, shake it up; vibration in the rush hour
サ 行け 認まれよ 泡沫バブルモーション
Go, be recognized, ephemeral bubble motion
一瞬で 虜に入る 壇上ハイ ぱいやぱいや
In an instant, I become a prisoner; Stage High, paiya paiya
ミスティック・クイ バイバイ仮面
Mystic Queen, Bye Bye Mask
今もあいつはどこかの国で どんな悪いことしてるやら
Even now, he's in some country, doing who knows what bad things
私はいつでもあんたの港
I'm always your harbor
疲れた時には戻っておいで
When you're tired, come back home
バ バ バ ババ ぱいやぱいや バイバイ 仮面は大不穏
Ba ba ba baba paiya paiya, Bye bye mask is greatly unsettling
バ バ バ ババ ぱいやぱいや 黄金の蝶 舞い上がれ
Ba ba ba baba paiya paiya, golden butterfly, soar up
ホレ ホレ 踊れよ 万歳万歳恋慕
Hey, hey, dance; banzai banzai love
セ 切な 生きろよ 瞬間クライマックス
P- Painfully, live it; instantaneous climax
浮世よ 忘れて更ける 壇上ハイ ぱいやぱいや
Floating world, forget it and grow late; Stage High, paiya paiya
ミスティック・クイ バイバイ仮面
Mystic Queen, Bye Bye Mask
ミスティック・クイ
Mystic Queen
バイバイ仮面
Bye Bye Mask
音乃瀬奏 Otonose Kanade
Otonose Kanade
一条莉々華 Ichijou Ririka
Ichijou Ririka
儒烏風亭らでん Juufuutei Raden
Juufuutei Raden
轟はじめ Todoroki Hajime
Todoroki Hajime
火威青 Hiiragi Ao
Hiiragi Ao
My heart starts skipping a beat
紐解いた心象
Unraveled mental image
様変わりセッションタイム
Changing session time
全然悪くないイマジネーション
A not-at-all bad imagination
誓いの霧は晴れ渡って
The fog of the vow clears away
悲しみには別れを告げる
I bid farewell to the sadness
Say my mind まっさらなホリデイ出して
Say my mind, start a brand new holiday
虹色の空 溜息を払い退け
Wiping away the sighs in the rainbow-colored sky
どれだけ幕見せようとしても
No matter how much of the act they try to show
君がいなければ
If you weren't here
なんの意味もない
Nothing would have meaning
かすり傷 切ない幻想
A scratch, a painful illusion
針の落ちないレコードさ
Like a record with no needle
たった今 猛烈な追い風 手にして
Right now, catching a fierce tailwind
Come on, Let's Roll!
怒涛 吹き荒れる向かい風にも心
Even against a raging headwind, my heart...
なびかせて
...will let it flutter
飛びのって To the Future
Hop on, to the future
ライジングスターって お出まし Re-STAR-T LINE
A rising star appears at the Re-STAR-T LINE
高鳴ってしまえば
Once the excitement builds
またたく間に広がる解放区
An open field spreads out in the blink of an eye
一挙一動 全てがドラマ
Every single move is a drama
待ちわびた場面に Re-STAR-T LINE
At the scene we've been waiting for, Re-STAR-T LINE
代わる代わる 踊るパノラマ
A rotating, dancing panorama
満ち溢れる フィーリングラデーション
Overflowing with a feeling of gradation
始まりの その時が来た
The time for the beginning has come
Nothing's impossible
むかし むかし 聞かせたいセカイ
A world from long, long ago I want you to hear
この先はまだ誰も知らない正解
From here on, a correct answer no one knows yet
傍観してるだけじゃ 味気ない
Just being a bystander is dull
リアルタイムで つむぎあって
Weave it together in real-time
派手に書き換えるモーション
Motion that flashy rewrites it all
後の祭りでも I don't mind
Even if it's too late, I don't mind
奔放 抜き差しならないシチュエーション
A wild, inescapable situation
行けるとこまで行ってみたーい！
I want to go as far as I can!
選択肢いらない Get out of my way
Don't need options, get out of my way
独り言は鳴らして
Let the soliloquy ring out
憂いもつらぬくような まっすぐな痛みが
A direct pain that pierces through even sorrow
伴ったとしても
Even if it comes with it
この仲間たちと 最果てまで
With these friends, to the ends of the earth
Keep running to the end
飛びのって To the Future
Hop on, to the future
ライジングスターって お出まし Re-STAR-T LINE
A rising star appears at the Re-STAR-T LINE
高鳴ってしまえば
Once the excitement builds
またたく間に広がる解放区
An open field spreads out in the blink of an eye
一挙一動 全てがドラマ
Every single move is a drama
待ちわびた場面に Re-STAR-T LINE
At the scene we've been waiting for, Re-STAR-T LINE
代わる代わる 踊るパノラマ
A rotating, dancing panorama
満ち溢れる フィーリングラデーション
Overflowing with a feeling of gradation
飛びのって You raise me up
Hop on, you raise me up
怖れるものはない Re-STAR-T LINE
There's nothing to fear at the Re-STAR-T LINE
きれいな朝焼けが
The beautiful sunrise...
透明な明日を照らすよ
...will light up a transparent tomorrow
Re-STAR-T LINE
Ah...
ポポポポポ！
Popopopopo!
ちょっと大丈夫ですか？
Are you okay?
喋れる？
Can you speak?
自己紹介始まるけれど。
Self-introductions are starting.
ポポポポポポ？
Popopopopopopo?
皆さん、ヘイ、ココカナタ〜！
Everyone, hey, here's Kanata~!
轟けキャッチフレーズ！
Let the catchphrase roar!
握力50キロ！
Grip strength: 50kg!
ギュッギュッ！握りつぶしちゃうぞ！
Squeeze squeeze! I'll crush you!
ホロライブ4期生、かなたんこと天音かなたです！よろしくお願いします！
Hololive 4th gen, Amane Kanata, also known as Kanatan! Pleased to meet you!
ポポポポポ！ありがとう！
Popopopopo! Thank you!
そして。
And now...
ポポポ、ポポポ。
Popopo, popopo.
ちょっと皆さん、今ポルちゃんが...
Wait, everyone, right now Pol-chan...
自分の名前が分からなくなってるんだけど。
...has forgotten her own name.
こういうのやってくれる？
Will you do something for me?
3文字で、この子に名前を教えてあげられますか？
In three syllables, can you tell her what her name is?
じゃあ僕、せーのっていうから、皆さんお願いしますね。
Okay, I'll say "Ready, go!", so everyone, please.
この子の名前は、せーの！
This girl's name is... Ready, go!
ポルカ！
Polka!
戻ったー！
I'm back!
戻ってきた！やばい！
I'm back! Oh my god!
おまるポルカです！皆楽しんでるかー！
I'm Omaru Polka! Is everyone having fun?!
イェーイ！
Yay!
盛り上がってるかー！
Are you guys pumped up?!
最高！
Awesome!
やあ、というわけで、うちらリグロスです！
Hey, so, we are ReGLOSS!
違うだろ！
No, we're not!
やめてください、そんな。
Stop it, don't say that.
全く台本にないことを。
Saying things that are totally not in the script.
いや、めちゃくちゃ良かった、ここまで。熱い熱い！
No, it's been amazing so far. So hot, so hot!
ね、熱い熱い。
Right? So hot.
最初のポルカの「ポ」から始まったけど、どうしようかと思ったよ。
It started with my "po", and I wondered what was going to happen.
いや、凄かった。
It was incredible.
やったよー！凄かったよ。テンション爆上げだよ、ポで。
We did it! It was amazing. My tension is through the roof, because of the "po".
あの...
Um...
ありがとうみんな！
Thank you everyone!
みんなー！
Everyone!
サンキュー！サンキュー！
Thank you! Thank you!
ですわ！もう超よかったね！
That's it! It was so good!
いやよかった、もう。
Yeah, it really was.
ベールズのもう最高！
Baelz was just the best!
天、本当に... かっこよかったね。
Man, it was really... cool, wasn't it?
めっちゃマジで！
Seriously, totally!
そしてね、船長がね...
And then, Sencho...
ええ、来ちゃったね。
Yeah, she came out.
パイパイしましたよ。
She did a "bye-bye."
しましたね。
She did.
よかったね、みんな。よかった。
It was great, wasn't it everyone? It was great.
そしてリグロスも最高だった！
And ReGLOSS was also amazing!
やばマジで、本当に。
Insane, seriously, really.
テンション超上がるわ！
I'm so hyped up!
あー、みんな！
Ah, everyone!
配信もどう？盛り上がってる？盛り上がってるわ！
How about the stream? Are you hyped? You are hyped!
配信のみんなー！見てるかー！見てるかー！
Everyone on the stream! Are you watching! Are you watching!
よかった、かっこよかったって言っています。
They're saying "It was good," "It was cool."
はい、かっこよかったと言っていますというわけで。
Yes, they're saying it was cool, and so...
はい。
Yes.
うちらも、うちらもかっこいいよな？
We're, we're cool too, right?
かっこいいよな！
We're cool!
イェーイ！どうですか？どうですか？
Yay! How about it? How about it?
いいじゃんいいじゃん！かわいい、かわいい！
Nice, nice! Cute, cute!
スカートの模様何それ？
What's that pattern on your skirt?
まあね。あら可愛い。
Well, you know. Oh, how cute.
ちょっとセクシーじゃない？
Isn't it a bit sexy?
あー、みんな、あ、ペンライト綺麗だね、あの、ありがとう！
Ah, everyone, oh, the penlights are beautiful, um, thank you!
うわー、綺麗！
Wow, beautiful!
ありがとうね。嬉しい。
Thank you. I'm happy.
いっちょウェーブでもやっておきますか？やっておきますか！
Shall we do a wave? Let's do it!
じゃあこっち行くか。こっち行くか。
Then let's go this way. Let's go this way.
できるかな？見ようね、こうワーってするやつ。
Can we do it? Let's watch, the "waah" kind of thing.
えっ、ワーってするやつね。こっちから行ったらワーだからね。
Uh, the "waah" kind of thing. If it goes from here, it's "waah."
ワーってするやつね。分かった。
The "waah" kind of thing. Got it.
いけるか？フィーリングで、なんとなくで行こう！
Can you do it? Let's just go with the feeling!
せーの！
Ready, go!
うわあああ！
Woooooaaah!
戻る？戻るこれ？戻る！あ、戻ってきた！
Coming back? Is it coming back? It's back! Ah, it came back!
戻ってきたー！すごーい！
It came back! Amazing!
ありがとう！ありがとう！
Thank you! Thank you!
めっちゃ楽しい。
So much fun.
幸せ。
Happy.
幸せ？
Happy?
もうずっとあと1時間とかで喋りますか？
Shall we talk for another hour or so?
はい。じゃあ、というわけで、これでおしまい...
Yes. Well, so, this is the end...
やめろやめろ嘘です嘘です、すみません。
Stop, stop, just kidding, just kidding, sorry.
え？
Eh?
ライヤー、ライヤー。
Liar, liar.
え？ライヤー、ライヤー？
Eh? Liar, liar?
ライヤーですよ。
Liar.
なんて言っておりますけれども。
Or so she says.
とてもたぶん緊張してると思いますね、かなたさんも。
I think Kanata-san is probably very nervous too.
あー、もう、緊張しますよ。
Ah, man, I'm nervous.
誰だか分かんないんですけれど皆さん、かなたーって言ってみてください、かなたーって。
I don't know who it is, but everyone, please say "Kanata," "Kanata."
ふざけんじゃねえよ。
Don't mess with me.
かなたー！
Kanata!
やったー！あー、よかったね。
Yay! Ah, that was great.
嬉しい。
I'm happy.
嬉しい、これはめちゃくちゃ嬉しい。
Happy, I'm super happy about this.
ありがとう。
Thank you.
これからもさ、いろんなホロメンがここで喋ると思うから、その時もいっぱいペンライト振って応援してあげてね。
Various Holo-members will talk here from now on, so please shake your penlights and support them then too.
是非応援してくださいね。
Please do support them.
ハイ！緊張して大変なことになってるメンバーもいっぱいいますから。
Yes! There are many members who are so nervous they're a mess.
大変なことに、あー確かに。
A mess... ah, true.
そうですよ。逆立ちとかね、楽屋でしてるメンバーいた気がする。
That's right. I think I saw a member doing handstands in the dressing room.
いない、いない、さすがにいません。
No, no, surely not.
はい。
Yes.
というわけでね、あ、これあれじゃない？
So, anyway, oh, isn't it this?
読んで読んで、ハッシュタグ、かなた。
Read it, read it, the hashtag, Kanata.
ハッシュタグ、はい、皆さん！
Hashtag, yes, everyone!
ハッシュタグ、ホロライブフェスエキスポ25アンダーバーデイワンで感想SNSにいっぱいポストしてくださいね。
Please post lots of your impressions on SNS with the hashtag #hololivefesEXPO25_DAY1.
終わったらいっぱい。あの...
Lots when it's over. Um...
あのネットで見てるお前らもな！
And you guys watching online too!
よろしく！
Please do!
見てるぞ！あとで見に行くからな！
I'm watching! I'll go look later!
そうだ、見に行くからね。
That's right, we'll go look.
本当に行くんだからな。ずっとトレンド入りさせてくれよな。
We're really going. Keep us trending, okay?
そうだよ、よろしくね。
That's right, please do.
ありがとう。
Thank you.
そしてここにいるみんなが盛り上げてくれればもっともっとトレンドが乗っていくはず。
And if everyone here hypes it up, it should trend even more.
いえーい！最高に一緒にステージ作り上げていこうぜ！
Yay! Let's build the best stage together!
いこうぜー！
Let's go!
そして配信の皆様にお知らせがあります。
And we have an announcement for those watching the stream.
なんだってー！
What?!
無料パートはここまでです！
The free segment ends here!
いえーい！もう一回、ここまでです！
Yay! One more time, it's until here!
早すぎるって！
It's too soon!
早すぎる、分かる。もっとやってほしいよね。
Too soon, I know. You want us to do more, right?
でもでもでもでも、この後もすっごいいろんな人たちが、いっぱい楽しいことするからさ。
But but but but, after this, so many people are going to do lots of fun things.
そうなんだよ。
That's right.
是非是非概要欄も今チェックしてチケット買ってください！
Please check the description box right now and buy a ticket!
よろしくお願いします！
Please do!
ハイ！
Yes!
ハイ、ありがとう。ありがとう。
Yes, thank you. Thank you.
あ、こっちの景色も見に行こう、ほら。
Ah, let's go see the view from here, look.
お、交代だ。
Oh, swapping.
イェーイ！かなたんはこれから何を歌うのでしょうか？楽しみですね。
Yay! I wonder what Kanatan will sing next? I'm looking forward to it.
みんな楽しんでいっぱい盛り上げていってね！
Everyone, have fun and hype it up!
ハイ！というわけでじゃあ我々はそろそろドロンして、次の方たちの曲を届けますか？
Yes! Well then, shall we clear out soon and deliver the next person's song?
ハイ！
Yes!
じゃあ、締めのあれはいつものあれで。
Then, for the closing, let's do the usual one.
いつものあれで、打ち合わせ通りいこうか。
The usual one, let's go as we discussed.
じゃあ行きます。
Then, here we go.
せーの！
Ready, go!
カラーライズ、ハーモニー！
Color Rise, Harmony!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended.
Thank you for watching.